[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "What on earth will Bill Maher say tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "I want to feel like I broke into the studio and took over and made them mad.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Maher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "It's not in their interest to do a deal, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "No probably about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "PERCENT": ["3 percent"], "PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Isn't it the Congress' job to present a jobs bill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well, I like this quote from Warren Buffett who says the way to get rid of the deficit, we should pass a law that says any time there's a deficit of more than 3 percent of GDP, all sitting members of Congress are ineligible for reelection.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "So it's all surprising to me that the people governing the country pander to that by this rhetoric of everything has to make a profit because that's the way you have a yardstick of success here, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, if you're talking about social mobility, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Why is it scary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Because it shows we're falling behind China.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Can America afford to see everything economically, militarily and so on as a threat in the way it has before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "But we would have to reconfigure all of our priorities.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Who's the threat that's going to invade us?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "See, many Americans, it seems to me -- I mean you say this stuff and I bet you get deluged with people calling you unpatriotic, un-American.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "But, I mean, is it time that America completely changed its philosophy on these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "What's patriotic is wanting your country to succeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "How many do the Chinese have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "None.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Shanghai"]}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "How many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "A hundred and 25,000 millionaires in Shanghai.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Palin or Bachmann?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I would need a gun to my head.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Is it possible in the current climate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Is America more or less racist now since Obama has been in power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "That's a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Are there other any of the Republican candidates so far that have emerged that you would see as potentially not life threatening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Well, you know, hopefully Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jimmy Carter"]}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Has there ever been a president in your lifetime who has been properly principled in your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Jimmy Carter was an amazingly principled president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "It attracts criticism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Well, not that, is there's a kind of expectation from this mass populace that you have to do certain things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "How do you think Obama is doing as president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "You know I love him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Is it, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What should he be doing right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "If a Democrat gets in and we don't attempt Democratic policy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "But what tag are you proudest of putting yourself to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I think I'm just practical.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "You hate their ideology, don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "But do you -- I mean you're a Democrat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "How would you describe yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I mean I'm certainly more in line with their thinking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Do you vote?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Democrat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Almost always.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Ever voted Republican?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2000"], "PERSON": ["McCain"]}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "When?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I voted for McCain in the 2000 primary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Have you aborted on being a sexaholic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "First of all, there is no such thing as a sexaholic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Are you still attending the Playboy mansion on a regular basis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "This always comes up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Doesn't that say something for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "You went in the grotto?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "I went in the grotto.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill"]}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Why don't they get on his case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "You are beginning to sound a bit defensive about this, Bill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "This job?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Is part of the trick of show business knowing when to leave the party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "What do you make of him as a human being?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Gee, what a question that is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "What is the secret of your age-defying presence today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Stress.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "What's your motivation to keep working now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Well, it's all I've ever really wanted to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "What would be your personal favorite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "I think the best movie I made was \"Glory\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Who have been the greatest male and female actors of your lifetime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Oh, heaven now you've got a long list.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "I mean, the most fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "What did you and Clint get up to that we don't know about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "That's for me to know and you to find out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "What do you make of the modern Hollywood scene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "Well, it's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "What would be the best piece of advice you would give to an up and coming actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "Act.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110715pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Simple as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "Doesn't matter where you go to work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]